Once upon a time, there was a girl who loved to dance very much.
The girl made the mistake of putting on a pair of red shoes that, once put on, would force her to dance for eternity.
The girl continued to dance day and night.
Oops. This is a different story.
Although, perhaps it is not so completely different after all.
What do you think of me?
I want to know.
I...
I'm a duck.
I'm really only a bird.
But what the prince sees is princess Tutu in her beautiful dress.
It's not me.
What did I do?
Just now.
Some things just don't change after a night's sleep.
Roo and Muto are still perfect for each other.
Fakir is still not nice.
I'm still a duck.
And outside the window, the sky is as wide open as ever.
There's no problem.
I am Roo.
I'm not anyone else.
That's who I've always been.
And who I always will be.
Roo.
Yes, what?
I want to know.
I want to know whether I love you or not, Roo.
I want to hear you say that you love me.
Yes, Roo, I love you.
Trust me, Muto.
You do love me.
Okay.
Then I do love you.
Do I really love you?
You do.
Then what is this that I feel when I'm thinking of Tutu?
Tutu.
Roo, maybe I'm actually...
Don't bother me with that nonsense.
What's going to happen?
Tell them to be ruined.
Will they be ruined?
They'll be ruined, won't they?
With this hand, I try to pierce Muto's heart.
On the grounds that doing so would be in Muto's best interests.
But since Muto himself wishes to regain his heart, what can I do, now that nothing I do can deter him?
Is there anything at all that remains for me, other than accepting fate and by his side without trembling?
How about the pizzeria?
What?
You don't know it?
It's the red building on Church Street.
No, I don't.
So what about this pizzeria?
What do you think?
Come on, what else?
Huh?
Your revenge!
What?
What revenge?
For your confession, of course.
Huh?
Now that Muto and Roo have fallen into ruin, this is your chance.
What do you mean?
Well, your confession the other day was kind of lukewarm.
No.
Now you can confess again.
Or rather get turned down again.
That's not what it was.
And what do you mean, ruin?
Huh?
In other words, now you can!
Confession, confession!
No, I can't!
You big coward!
You shouldn't roll down the hallway.
It's your fault, really?
You again, Miss Duck?
Oh, rolling down the hallway.
If you keep this up, I will have no choice but to have you marry me.
I...
I'm so sorry.
Something's rolling down the hall.
It's coming really fast!
What?
Miss Duckett!
If you roll down the hallway, you'll be forced to marry Mr. Cat.
Get out!
Ah!
Hey, what about inviting him to your house?
House?
Oh!
Where is your house, Duck?
Uh, the lake?
The lake?
I mean, it's out towards the lake.
So I guess it's outside town, huh?
Hmm.
After all, the only thing in town is that old pot.
What?
All right, everyone.
That will be it for the beginner class lesson.
The next hour...
Hmm?
Ah!
The private lesson for the advanced class will be starting after this, so please vacate the
room immediately.
If you dawdle or hang about, I will have you marry me!
I got it in the first try.
Um, Miss Gotet's dawdling and hanging about.
It seems you'll have to get married.
Meow!
Huh?
Mewtwo!
Your chance!
Oh!
Wonderful as ever, huh?
Doesn't look like there's an opening for Duck!
Huh?
Opening for Duck!
Don't lose heart, Duck!
That's right!
After all, we already knew this was the case!
I know.
Mewtwo is perfect for real.
I know that I'm just a duck.
What do you think of me?
I want to know.
I know exactly what I think of Mewtwo.
But I can't say it.
If you choose to become Princess Chutu, you can save your dear Prince.
But if you proclaim your love to him, you'll turn into a speck of light and vanish.
I know.
But somehow, my heart still aches.
You don't have to change at all.
You're fine just as you are.
Why must you keep trying to change when I don't want to?
When I want things to stay as they are.
Princess Chutu?
What in the world is there that I need fear?
Ridiculous.
The Prince and the Crow.
The story that is written here is Mewtwo's tale.
The fate of a foolish prince who tried to protect the weak, but only ended up hurting himself and losing his own heart.
That's all.
May those who accept their fate be granted happiness.
May those who defy it be granted glory.
Your...
The story is continuing.
The story is alive.
Are you saying this is my fate?
Huh, is it sad for Mewto, for Roo, for Duck, or for...
You know, Roo, you really dance beautifully on point.
And when you and Mewto dance, it's always so wonderful.
I'd love to dance like that, but there's no way I can yet.
Did you want something?
Uh, well, earlier you mentioned Princess Choo Choo.
Just what are you prattling on about?
A fairy tale like that is of no importance.
You're your usual self.
Of course I am. I'm not going to change.
If you want to say something, hurry up.
There's nothing, really.
You know, I think the first person to dance on point was incredible.
Don't you?
There's a story about the toe shoes of the first person to dance on point.
Do you know what happened to them?
What? Uh, no.
Well, they were eaten.
They what?
By a person who worshipped that ballerina.
That's kind of amazing.
It's a stupid story.
Huh?
Strange.
What?
No.
Weird.
Huh?
What's strange?
I've never talked like this with another girl before.
Oh.
Do you hate this kind of thing?
I don't think I hate it.
Huh?
I'm glad.
So we can become even better friends, right?
You think?
Hey, hey Ru, teach me about going on point.
And why should I teach you?
Because we're friends.
You've got a lot of cheek.
Huh?
Hey Ru?
Now what?
Um, is that girl your friend too?
Where?
What girl is this?
She disappeared.
And that concludes today's lecture on Real!
Goodbye Ms. Ru.
I bid you good afternoon.
Do your best in detention.
Don't be close.
You're failures, I won't make you duck.
So duck, you can't go home yet?
Huh?
Yeah, I have to stay and wipe the windows as punishment.
Oh.
Friends.
That's the girl from...
She went into the art building.
So she studies drawing, huh?
Hi Ru!
Lady Ru?
What?
What's so hard about that?
Besides, we've walked together and talked all this time, so we're already friends now.
Thus it's Ru.
You're like a real princess, and you really suit each other, so I'm sure you'll get the golden apple too.
You really suit each other, so...
Suit each other?
It's just an idea you've got stuck in your head.
You may think you need me, but the simple fact remains I do not need you.
The person I need is Muto.
But the one Muto needs is...
Princess Tutu.
The person I need is Muto.
But the one Muto needs is...
Princess Tutu.
I wonder what it is I think of you, Fakir.
When I think of Rue.
When I think of you, Fakir.
And when I'm thinking about Princess Tutu...
I wonder what it is I think of you, Fakir.
When I think of Ru.
When I think of you, Fakir.
And when I'm thinking about Princess Tutu...
I wonder what it is I think of you, Fakir.
When I think of Rue, when I think of you, Fakir,
and when I'm thinking about Princess Tutu,
each one makes me feel different.
I've chosen to go, Fakir.
You're kidding, right?
I mean it.
What point is there?
Maybe there's something she can tell me about Tutu.
Muto's changing into...
a Muto that I don't know.
That is something that cannot be helped.
The way we think about things is worlds apart.
As you can see, even what we eat is quite different.
It is for these reasons that I do not wish to marry you.
And so I've no intention of changing my will.
My will.
Do you understand me now, Miss Gotent?
You're one of the ballet students.
Well, I'm really pretty terrible at drawing pictures.
That's because you're in ballet.
I'm bad at ballet too, though.
Oh, you are?
I'm sorry.
No, no, it's fine.
Mind if I take a peek?
Wow, it's great.
A drawing of Rue.
I'm so jealous of you.
Oh, did you draw these ones too?
Hang on, they're all drawings of Rue?
Well, Rue really is pretty, so I can totally understand.
Hey, this one's signed.
Your name is Malin?
Hey, that's a cute name.
My name's Duck.
I don't understand.
I don't really understand it myself.
I mean, I've always enjoyed doing life drawing with Miss Rue as the model,
but it used to be I wanted to draw other things too, like fruits and sceneries.
But now, I can only draw Miss Rue.
Princess Tutu?
Princess Tutu will change everything.
She'll change Muto.
At this rate, Muto will only grow more distant from me.
I won't allow that to happen.
Then what do you plan to do about it?
What?
A beautiful black swan.
Who is the heroine of this story?
Is it Princess Tutu?
Or is it Princess Cranky?
Princess Cranky the heroine?
It hurts when I try to draw anything else.
A story doesn't need two heroines now, does it?
And no prince needs two princesses.
Now, come and tell me what should happen next.
Please come dance with me, Miss Malin.
Who are you?
I don't know how to dance.
Don't worry.
Just dance freely.
The source of your pain is the false heart residing within your heart.
I'll remove it for you.
Then, once again, you'll be able to draw what you love.
Really?
Yes, you can go back to being your old self.
Thank you.
I'm so glad.
I just want to stay the same, never changing.
Yes, once again, Princess Tutu will change Mewtwo.
You'll change Mewtwo.
What's this?
Tootu, where are you?
What emotion are you?
I am the feeling of devotion.
You are a shard of the prince's heart, which he lost.
So, the feeling of devotion, is it?
Crazy.
I will not suffer you to return such a thing to Mewtwo.
What will you do?
I don't know.
What should I do?
No!
You had better forget about restoring any more heart shards to the prince.
Princess, but the prince told me, the prince told me that he wants to regain his heart.
Princess Tutu, I finally found you.
Why do you look at me that way?
Am I...
jagö
Kang?
Do you look at me that way?
Why?
Meinny?
What's wrong?
Stay away!
What's wrong? Stay away!
Am I not needed?
Krihi, why are you in such pain?
What?
Is there any way I can help you?
Who is Krihi?
Look here!
Be gone, you ugly crow!
Crow?
That's right, I am a crow.
And I alone am the true prima donna, Princess Krihi.
I'll take what I desire by force if need be.
Sks
With this
No, no no no no no no no come.
Judges
Do you with her?
Is here?
I haven't?
Wash
Was there a concern I fear?
Mewto and Kreh'i's wedding? With Bakir for a witness?
The legend you told me about as a child is swiftly becoming reality.
You'd be much better off forgetting this accursed tale.
Prince is a weird name. How about we call you Mewto?
Are you going to Kreh'i?
I feel I must run away.
What say you, Princess Tutu? Aren't we just perfect for each other?
All who love stories gather up.
B reconocer…
If you do, more pictures are what ha parece a dolly.
I take shape…
B
Main